{
"question": "一緒",
"answer": "いっしょ"
},
{
"question": "先週",
"answer": "せんしゅう"
},
{
"question": "白い",
"answer": "しろい"
},
{
"question": "二",
"answer": "に"
},
{
"question": "少ない",
"answer": "すくない"
},
{
"question": "赤い",
"answer": "あかい"
},
{
"question": "洗う",
"answer": "あらう"
},
{
"question": "嫌い",
"answer": "きらい"
},
{
"question": "立派",
"answer": "りっぱ"
},
{
"question": "暇",
"answer": "ひま"
},
{
"question": "お茶",
"answer": "おちゃ"
},
{
"question": "広い",
"answer": "ひろい"
},
{
"question": "去年",
"answer": "きょねん"
},
{
"question": "大好き",
"answer": "だいすき"
},
{
"question": "隣",
"answer": "となり"
},
{
"question": "女",
"answer": "おんな"
},
{
"question": "多分",
"answer": "たぶん"
},
{
"question": "切る",
"answer": "きる"
},
{
"question": "嫌",
"answer": "いや"
},
{
"question": "毎朝",
"answer": "まいあさ"
},
